abaenglish.com 2017-12-03

# Privacy Policy | ABA English | ABA English

**How do we use the information you provide?**

All information that you provide will be treated confidentially. Your personal data is only accessible to you and ABA English personnel who are at your service. This is guaranteed because our web pages are hosted on a secure server. The server which hosts our web and where your data is kept, offers the most advanced data protection system, so no one lacking authorization can access the information.

You are also informed that, in accordance with the provisions of Article 5 of Law 15/1999 on Protection of Personal Data (LOPD), your personal data will be held in files owned by ENGLISH WORLDWIDE, SL in order to adequately provide the requested services, fulfill the company’s billing and accounting requirements, conduct statistical analyses, verify credit cards and other forms of payment, as well as to email you marketing information that could be of interest.

Your personal information will be treated with the utmost confidentiality and the duty of secrecy required. ENGLISH WORLDWIDE, SL has adopted the technical and organizational measures defined in Royal Decree 1720/2007 of 21 December, which approves the Regulations for implementing Law 15/1999.

You can exercise your rights to access, change, oppose or delete your data by sending a written and signed request, including a photocopy of your ID card or other equivalent identification document, to: ENGLISH WORLDWIDE S.L., c/ Aribau, 240 – 7º – 08006 Barcelona. Spain.

**Google Analytics**

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, small pieces of information that are stored on your computer, to analyse the use you make of the website.

Google, on behalf of our website also uses this information to compile reports on website activity and provide other services related to the use of Internet services. The IP address transmitted by your browser within Google Analytics is not associated with other data of Google.

You can prevent the storage of cookies via an integrated browser functionality. However, note that if you disable storage, you cannot fully use all the functions of our website.

You can find more information on the use and protection of data in Google Analytics at [http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html) or [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en-GB](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en-GB) .

**Social plugins**

Our website includes social networking features such as Facebook and Twitter buttons. Such features may collect your IP address and information about the page you’re visiting and may set cookies to function properly. Interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policies of the company that offers them.

For more information on the scope of the data collection and its use by Facebook and Twitter, visit the pages [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php) and [http://twitter.com/privacy](http://twitter.com/privacy).

**Access, Revision and Deletion of your information**

You can access, review and correct registration information through your account page in “My Account”.

We will retain your information while your account is active or if we believe you may be able to return to be a user, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

You can request the cancellation of your personal data by e-mail or regular mail.

The application must contain at least the following information:

  * Username
  * Name and surname
  * Email address
  * Postal address

Please note that deleted data can still be viewed without being present in our systems, due to caching systems, search engines and the interconnection of the proxy servers and the like.
